

## Arthur Lynn E.

## Business Development Manager

Contact

Phone

639453163943

Address 39D Insurance Project8 Quezon City Philippines

Email arthurlynnwilliams01@gmail.com

Expertise

Forex Trading

Account Management

Sales / Business

Development

Lead Generation

**Customer Service** 

Fund Management Logistics

References

Sun Life Canada Von Montepiedra 639152342483

Security Bank

David Gio Dela Rosa

639178235163

Seda Hotle Jasmine Habulan 639559073432 Experienced Sales Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the events services industry, Logistics, Insurance, and Forex. I have been trading proprietarily for almost 3 years now. Excellent and diverse sales expertise

Educational

BS Hotel and Restaurant Management

2012 - 2016

July 2022-Present

Experiences

UNIRAMP

Overlook & manage sales team activities in a specific area and/or for specific accounts Maintain and provide a detailed and continuous sales report and forecast

Develop proposals, conduct sales conversations, give presentations

Actively understand each customer's strategic growth plans, technology, and needs Contacting potential clients via email and/or phone to establish rapport and set up meetings.

Lead a team to overlook and manage sales activities in a specific area and/or for specific accounts

Inxpress USA- Senior Sales Executive

January-July 2022

Provide and assist the current clients with their shipping inquiries. Upsell existing services to existing clients. Generate more clients via cold calls and emails. Guide new clients on how to use the systems. Monitor and track shipping transactions both domestic and international

Mtrading-Sales Account Manager

March 2021- July 2021

Manage the entire sales process from identifying prospects via cold calling and cold email and face-to-face. Develop business and implement a sales plan. Generate own leads. Sell auto trading platforms and systems. Conduct webinars teaching clients the basics of the platform and how to trade forex.

Nature Forex- Sales Account Manager

September 2020- March 2021

Manage the entire sales process from identifying prospects via cold calling and cold email and face-to-face. Develop business and implement a sales plan. Generate own leads. Sell auto trading platforms and systems. Maintains updated professional and technical knowledge of Forex market information

BPI-Philamlife: Bancassurance Sales Executive

March,2019-Febuary.,2020

Carry out continuous lead generation. Set appointments whether over the phone or face to face. Conduct financial needs analysis and recommend customized solutions. Strengthen customer relationships. Cross-sell and up-sell BPI-PHILAMLIFE products to BPI customers Establish, maintain, and grow a good relationship with bank partners Prepare submit and analyze sales report on a regular basis

Customer Service Representative at VXI Global Holdings

December, 2017- January 2019

(Financial Account: Xoom)

Provide Customer Service for Remittance. Help Customers process a transaction and make changes to their account. Verify the Customer's account for Security.

-Organized outbound calls for follow-ups regarding customers' transactions and upon their request. Help customers to dispute charges on their account.